Guide to the Bates Worldwide, Inc. Records, 1934-2005 and undated RL.00090
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- New Business Series, 1973-2003 and undated, bulk 1993-2003, 45 boxes
  - Companies Subseries, 1973-2003 and undated, bulk 1993-2003
    - Qwest, 2002 (Box NB31)
    - Radio Shack, 2001 (Box NB31)
    - Ralston Purina
      - Correspondence, 2001, 2 folders (Box NB31)
      - Presentation on cat treats, 1999 Feb. 3 (Box NB31)
    - Rayovac Corporation, 2001, 2 folders (Box NB31)
    - RCA (Radio Corporation of America): see eBook (Box NB31)
    - RCI presentation, 1999 July 7 (Box NB31)
    - Reckitt-Benckiser
      - Briefing information, 2000, 2 folders (Box NB31)
      - Media plan, undated (Box NB31)
      - Media presentation, 2000 Mar. 21 (Box NB31)
      - Request for information, 2000 Feb. 10 (Box NB31)
      - Request for proposal, undated (Box NB31)
      - Miscellaneous, 2001, 3 folders (Box NB31)
      - Disk 39. Presentation (Box NB31)
    - Red Cross, 2002 (Box NB32)
    - Reebok International/ Rockport Company, 2000 (Box NB32)
    - Relpax
      - Presentations, 1999, 2 folders (Box NB32)
      - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box NB32)
    - Re/Max
      - Debrief letter, 2002 Oct. 21 (Box NB32)
      - Request for information, 1999 Nov. 10 (Box NB32)
    - Remy Amerique (Cointreau), 2001 (Box NB32)
    - Renaissance Hotels and Resorts, 1996 (Box NB32)
    - Resort Condominiums briefing book, 1999 May 28, 2 folders (Box NB32)
    - Resume.com, 2002 (Box NB32)
    - Rezulin (Parke-Davis/Warner-Lambert)
      - Mailings, 1999 (Box NB32)
      - Presentations
        - Brand Essence, 1999 (Box NB32)
        - Science of New Hope, 1999 (Box NB32)
    - Rhone-Poulenc Rorer Pharmaceuticals, undated (Box NB32)
    - [Ritz-Carlton, response to request, circa 1998: Removed to Box NB46] (Box NB32)
    - Royal Mail U.S. Inc. presentation, 1998 Mar. 23 (Box NB32)
    - Royal Olympic Cruises, 2001 (Box NB32)
    - R.R. Donnelley and Sons, 2002 (Box NB32)
    - Rubenstein Associates, 2002 (Box NB32)
    - Ruido Group, 2001 (Box NB33)
    - Ryder briefing book, 1997 Oct. 7 (Box NB33)
    - Samsonite Corporation, 2000 (Box NB33)
    - Samsung Group
      - Briefing book, 2002 June, 5 folders (Box NB33)
      - Introduction letter, 2000 Aug. 2 (Box NB33)
    - Sara Lee Coffees, 2001 (Box NB33)
    - Sara Lee Lingerie
      - Bali competitive review, 2000 May 22 (Box NB33)
      - Debrief, 2000 May 26 (Box NB33)
      - Request for information, 2000 (Box NB33)
      - Request for proposal, 2000, Folder 1 of 3 (Box NB33)
      - Request for proposal, 2000 (continued), Folders 2-3 of 3 (Box NB34)
    - Sauza (Allied Domecq)
      - Mailings, 1998-2000 (Box NB34)
      - Presentation, 1999 Feb. 23 (Box NB34)
    - SBC Communications
      - Bell South request for proposal, 2000, 2 folders (Box NB34)
      - Wanamaker Associates, 2000 June 18 (Box NB34)
    - Schering-Plough
      - Request for information, 2002 (Box NB34)
      - Response, 2002 Nov. 13 (Box NB34)
    - Schick-Wilkinson Sword, 2003 (Box NB34)
    - Scholastic Entertainment, 2002 (Box NB34)
    - S.C. Johnson & Sons, 2001, 3 folders (Box NB34)
    - Scunci (L & N Sales and Marketing), 2002 (Box NB34)
    - Seagate Technology, 2001 (Box NB34)
    - Sears Roebuck & Co., 2000 (Box NB34)
    - Sempra Energy Solutions, 2000 (Box NB34)
    - Serta, 1999 (Box NB34)
    - Sharp Electronics, 2001 (Box NB34)
    - Sheraton presentations, 1999, 2 folders (Box NB35)
    - Showtime, 2002 (Box NB35)
    - SHR, 1999 (Box NB35)
    - Slomin's, 2002 (Box NB35)
    - Sole Technology, 2002 (Box NB35)
    - Sonicare, 2003 (Box NB35)
    - Spalding Sports Worldwide, 2000 (Box NB35)
    - Spectrum United, undated (Box NB35)
    - Speedy (Bates Canada), undated (Box NB35)
    - Sprint, 2002 (Box NB35)
    - Stanley Steamer request for information, 2002 July 30 (Box NB35)
    - Staples
      - Introduction letter, 2000 (Box NB35)
      - Request for information, 2000 (Box NB35)
      - Request for proposal, 2000 (Box NB35)
      - Disk 24. Office document (Box NB35)
        Disk contains a powerpoint file, and six video files that are part of the powerpoint presentation
    - [Starwood Hotels and Resorts, response to request for proposal, 2001 Oct. 11: Removed to Box NB47] (Box NB35)
    - Starwood Lodgings
      - Correspondence, 2001 (Box NB35)
      - Presentation, 2001 (Box NB35)
      - Request for information, 2001 Oct. 11, 2 folders (Box NB35)
      - Request for proposal, 2000 (Box NB35)
    - Starz!/Encore (Liberty Media), 2003, 2 folders (Box NB35)
    - Stride Rite, 2003 (Box NB35)
    - Sunkist Growers, Inc.
      - Presentations, 1999, Folder 1 of 3 (Box NB35)
      - Presentations, 1999 (continued), Folders 2-3 of 3 (Box NB36)
      - Miscellaneous information, 1999 (Box NB36)
    - Suzuki: see American Suzuki (Box NB36)
    - Symbol Technologies presentation, 2001 Nov. 5 (Box NB36)
    - Target Corporation, 2002 (Box NB36)
    - Tetra Pak, 2000 (Box NB36)
    - Texaco: see Chevron-Texaco (Box NB36)
    - Thomasville Furnishings, 2001 (Box NB36)
    - Tickets.com, 2000 Jan. 17 (Box NB36)
    - Tiffany & Co., 2002 (Box NB36)
    - Timex, 2000 (Box NB36)
    - T.J. Maxx, 2000 (Box NB36)
    - Toshiba, 2002, 2 folders (Box NB36)
    - Transworld Airlines, 2001 (Box NB36)
    - T. Rowe Price member retirement, 1999 (Box NB36)
    - Truserv Corp., 1999 (Box NB36)
    - TV Guide, 2000 (Box NB36)
    - Tyco International, 2000 (Box NB36)
    - UDate.com, 2000 (Box NB36)
    - Ultram (Ortho-McNeal Pharmaceuticals), 1999 (Box NB36)
    - Unisys Corporation, 2000
      - Introduction letter, 2000 May 15 (Box NB36)
      - Request for information, 2000 July 5 (Box NB36)
      - Request for proposal, 2000 (Box NB36)
      - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box NB36)
    - United Airlines, 2002, 3 folders (Box NB36)
    - United Parcel Service (UPS), 2000 (Box NB36)
    - Universal Studios, 2000 (Box NB36)
    - Uptown Nails, 2000 (Box NB36)
    - U.S. Airways, 2001 (Box NB36)
    - U.S. Beverages LLC (Grolsch), 2002 (Box NB36)
    - U.S. Navy (Box NB37)
      - Briefing book, 2000 July 27 (Box NB37)
      - Briefing information, 2000, 2 folders (Box NB37)
      - De-brief letter, 2000 Sept. 21 (Box NB37)
      - National youth anti-drug media campaign, undated (Box NB37)
      - Past performance questionnaire, 2001 (Box NB37)
      - Presentations,undated, 2 folders (Box NB37)
    - U.S. Peace Corps, 1991-1993, 2003, 3 folders (Box NB38)
    - U.S. Postal Service (USPS)
      - Prequalification for advertising, 2000 (Box NB38)
      - Response, 2000 (Box NB38)
    - UUNet mailings, 1999-2000 (Box NB38)
    - Viewtrade.com, 2000 (Box NB38)
    - Virgin Atlantic Airways, 2000, 2 folders (Box NB38)
    - Virgin Records, 2002 (Box NB38)
    - Visa USA, 2000 (Box NB38)
    - Vlasic Pickles, 1973 (Box NB38)
    - Wal-Mart.com, 2000 (Box NB38)
    - Walt Disney Company, 2001 (Box NB38)
    - Warner-Lambert request for information, 1994 Feb. 1 (Box NB38)
    - Waste Management, 2001 (Box NB38)
    - WebMD
      - Briefing books, 2000, Folders 1-4 of 6 (Box NB38)
      - Briefing books, 2000 (continued), Folders 1-4 of 6 (Box NB39)
      - Pitch team meeting, 2000, 3 folders (Box NB39)
    - Weider Nutrition International information letter, 2000 Sept. 8 (Box NB39)
    - Welch Foods, 2001 (Box NB39)
    - Western Union, 2001 (Box NB39)
    - Westvaco mailings, 1995-1996 (Box NB39)
    - Wheretheheckisit.com, 2002 (Box NB39)
    - W Hotels, 2001 (Box NB39)
    - Williams-Sonoma, undated (Box NB39)
    - Winn-Dixie
      - Correspondence, 2000, 2002, 2 folders (Box NB39)
      - Request for Proposal, 2000 (Box NB39)
      - Response, 2000 Aug. 14 (Box NB39)
    - Wiz (electronics chain), 2002 (Box NB39)
    - Worth.com, 2000 (Box NB39)
    - Xerox Corporation, 2000 (Box NB39)
    - Zany Brainy, 2000 (Box NB39)
    - Zenith Electronics Corporation, 2000 (Box NB39)
  - Large Format Materials
    - General Files
      - Marketing presentation portfolio, 2002 (Box NB40)
        Luggage tag reads Paul Levine, Chief Marketing Officer. Includes advertisements from Brown and Williamson, Honda, Nike, Tommy Hilfiger, Warner-Lambert and Wendy's
      - Media: Bates Worldwide print advertising examples, circa 2000 (Box NB41)
    - Agencies
      - Fitch:Worldwide, overview, undated (Box NB41)
      - Grey Advertising, Response to Coldwell Banker, 2001 (Box NB41)
      - Leonhardt Group, report Design: Strategy for Business, 2000 (Box NB41)
    - Companies
      - Alltel proposal, 2001 (Box NB42)
      - Bell South, article on diversity program, in Human Resources Executive, 2001 Oct. 1 (Box NB42)
      - Carnival Cruise Lines, promotional gargoyle in box, 2001 (Box NB43)
      - Hire.com presentation, 2001 (Box NB44)
      - IKEA print advertising examples (Bates North America), 2001 (Box NB44)
      - Nikon, response to request, 2002 (Box NB45)
        Portfolio of advertising examples from clients including the Ad Council, National Geographic, Nokia, Sauza, and the Whitney Museum.
      - Nokia, Bates America's Vital Statistics, 2001 Nov. 16 (Box NB46)
      - Ritz-Carlton, response to request, circa 1998 (Box NB46)
      - Starwood Hotels and Resorts, response to request for proposal, 2001 Oct. 11 (Box NB47)
        Package in the form of Batesopoly, a parody of the Parker Brothers, Monopoly board game.
- Print Books Series, 1957-2003, 132 boxes
  Print proofs, tear sheets and photocopies of print advertisements maintained in print books by the Print Production Department, which was responsible for producing these advertisements in various sizes, colors, and shapes. Entries in the books were apparently made as the advertisements were created. The print books thus reflect Bates' domestic client roster over time and constitute a representative sampling of Bates' North American output for the years covered. (For examples of Bates' international work, see the Creative Department Series.) Major clients represented include Avis, Campbell's Soup Company, Carter-Wallace, Cunard Lines, Foot Locker, Hyundai, Kal Kan, Lancaster, M&M/Mars, Miller Brewing Co., Paddington, Panasonic, Prudential-Bache, T. Rowe Price, Trans-World Airlines (TWA), U.S. Navy, Warner-Lambert, Wendy's International, and Westvaco. The files are organized into two lists--chronological and alphabetical. There is considerable date overlap in the chronological listings, largely due to the vaying durations of Bates' client relationships.
  - Chronological List, 1957-2003
    Arranged by year, then alphabetically by client contained in each print book
    - 1957-1969
      - Savings and Loan Associations (Box PB1)
        Some advertisements by McCann Erickson agency
    - 1970-1975
      - Miller Brewing Company (Box PB2)
    - 1972-1980
      - Savings and Loan Associations (Box PB3)
    - 1976-1977
      - M & M/Mars, Panasonic (Box PB4)
      - U.S. Navy (Box PB5)
    - 1976-1979
      - Miller Brewing Company (Box PB6)
    - 1978-1979
      - American Chicle, Electrolux, Ocean Spray, Pfizer (Box PB7)
      - Borden, Breck (Box PB8)
      - Bristol Myers, International Continental Baking (see also Wonder Bread), Prudential-Bache (Box PB9)
      - Carter-Wallace, Chase Manhattan (Box PB10)
      - Colgate-Palmolive, Ted Bates (Box PB11)
      - Conair, Coors, RCA, Standard Brands Company, Thompson Medical (see also Slim Fast) (Box PB12)
      - Electrolux, Maybelline, Nabisco, Warner-Lambert (Box PB13)
      - Hefty, Hertz, Mobil, Schweppes (Box PB14)
      - Industrial National Bank, Kal Kan, Playtex (Box PB15)
      - JADOR (joint military recruiting) (Box PB16)
      - M & M/Mars, Panasonic (Box PB17)
    - 1980
      - U.S. Navy (Box PB18)
    - 1980-1981
      - American Chicle, JADOR (joint military recruiting), U.S. Navy, Warner-Lambert (Box PB19)
      - Borden, Breck, Colgate-Palmolive, Ted Bates (Box PB20)
      - Carter, Clairol, Maybelline, M&M/Mars (Box PB21)
      - General Foods, Kool (Brown and Williamson) (Box PB22)
      - HBO (Box PB23)
      - Joseph Garneau, Prudential (Box PB24)
      - Kal Kan, Mego, Playtex, RCA (Box PB25)
      - Paddington Corporation (Box PB26)
      - Panasonic (Box PB27)
    - 1980-1982
      - Backer Spielvogel Bates, Campbell's (Box PB28)
    - 1980-1983
      - Savings & Loan Associations (Box PB29)
    - 1981-1983
      - Bonjour, Red Lobster (Box PB30)
    - 1981-1986
      - Helene Curtis, Noxell, Red Lobster, Seven-Up (Box PB31)
    - 1982
      - Paddington Corporation (Box PB32)
    - 1982-1983
      - American Chicle, Duffy-Mott, RCA, R.J. Reynolds, Schweppes, Ted Bates, Warner-Lambert (Box PB33)
      - American Cyanamid, Carter-Wallace, Electrolux, Nivea (Beiersdorf), Rose Holland House (Box PB34)
      - Colgate-Palmolive, Hefty, Kal Kan, Wonder Bread (see also International Continental Baking) (Box PB35)
      - Coors, Maybelline, Piker George, Prudential (Box PB36)
      - Dr. Scholl's, Ted Bates, U.S. Navy (Box PB37)
      - General Foods, Joseph Garneau, M & M/Mars, Pfizer (Box PB38)
      - HBO, TV Cable Magazine (Box PB39)
      - Miller Brewing Company (including Calgary, Löwenbräu, Meister Bräu) (Box PB40)
      - Panasonic (Box PB41)
    - 1983-1984
      - Paddington Corporation (Box PB42)
    - 1983-1988
      - Campbell's (including V-8 juice drink) (Box PB43)
    - 1984-1985
      - AVIS, Commodore Computers, R.J. Reynolds (Box PB44)
      - Colgate, International Baking Company (ITT-CBC), Kal Kan, Michelob (Anheuser Busch), Mobil (Box PB45)
    - 1984-1986
      - American Cyanamid, Carter-Wallace, Cinemax (Box PB46)
      - DHL, General Foods, Louis Rich, M&M/Mars, Panasonic, Pfizer (Visine) (Box PB46A)
      - Dr. Scholl's, Panasonic (Box PB47)
      - Holland House, Ted Bates, U.S. Navy (Box PB48)
      - NCR (Box PB49)
      - Schweppes, Warner-Lambert (Box PB50)
    - 1985-1986
      - Hyundai (Box PB51)
      - Paddington Corporation (Box PB52)
      - Parliament (Philip Morris) (Box PB53)
    - 1986
      - General Foods, Joseph Garneau, Louis Rich, M & M/Mars, Pfizer (Box PB54)
    - 1986-1988
      - Magnavox, Philips (Box PB55)
      - Miller Brewing Company (Box PB56)
    - 1986-1990
      - Fisher Price (Box PB57)
    - 1987
      - American Cynamid, Carter-Wallace, Dr. Scholl's, Maybelline (Box PB58)
      - Cinemax, M&M/Mars, Uncle Ben's (Box PB58A)
      - Kal Kan, Panasonic, Ted Bates (Box PB59)
      - Prudential-Bache (Box PB60)
    - 1987-1988
      - Hyundai (Box PB61)
      - Paddington Corporation (Box PB62)
      - Parliament (Philip Morris) (Box PB63)
    - 1987-1989
      - Avis (Box PB64)
      - CBS (Box PB65)
    - 1988
      - Carter-Wallace, M & M/Mars (Box PB66)
      - Cinemax (Box PB67)
      - Dole, Kal Kan, Pfizer, Uncle Ben's, U.S. Mint (Box PB68)
    - 1988-1989
      - Miller Brewing Company (Box PB69)
    - 1988-1990
      - Prudential-Bache (Box PB70)
    - 1989
      - Ad Council (Backer Spielvogel Bates) (Box PB71)
      - Hyundai, Northern Telecom (Nortel) (Box PB72)
    - 1989-1990
      - Kal Kan, M&M/Mars (Box PB73)
      - Parliament (Philip Morris) (Box PB74)
    - 1989-1991
      - Backer Spielvogel Bates (Box PB75)
    - 1989-1992
      - Ad Council, American Association of Advertising Agencies (AAAA), American Foundation for the Blind, Metropolitan Museum of Art, Positano, St. Francis Friends of the Poor (Box PB75A)
      - Burroughs-Wellcome, Campbell's, Magnavox (North American Philips) (Box PB76)
    - 1990
      - Avis (Box PB77)
      - British Airways (Box PB78)
      - Hyundai, Jhirmack, Northern Telecom (Nortel), Webster Industries (Box PB79)
      - Xerox (Box PB80)
    - 1990-1991
      - New York Racing Association (Box PB81)
    - 1990-1992
      - CBS, Northern Telecom (Nortel), Webster Industries (Box PB82)
      - Miller Brewing Company (Box PB83)
    - 1991-1992
      - Kal Kan, M & M/Mars (Box PB84)
      - Lancaster (see also Joop!), Uncle Ben's, Wendy's (Box PB85)
    - 1991-1993
      - British Airways, Best Foods, Lancaster (see also Joop!), Mustang (Joop! Jeans), Scentstrips (see also Lancaster) (Box PB86)
    - 1991-2000
      - Foot Locker, Joop! (see also Lancaster), Kinney, Lipitor, Lucky Strike (Brown & Williamson), Magnavox, Miller Brewing Company, Nair, Neosporin, Prevacid, Rezulin (Box PB87)
    - 1992
      - Avis (Box PB88)
      - Best Foods, Burroughs-Wellcome, Carter-Wallace, Haddad (Box PB89)
    - 1992-1993
      - New York Racing Association (Box PB90)
      - TWA (Box PB91)
    - 1992-1994
      - Campbell's, JRAP (Joint Recruiting Program), Magnavox (North American Philips) (Box PB92)
    - 1992-2001
      - AIDS Foundation, Arrid, Avis, Benadryl, Brightlane.com, Cabletrom, Campbell's, CDW, Champs, Clinique, Caribbean Tourism, Cunard, Cinnaburst (see also Warner-Lambert), Derivion, EDS, Electrolux, Estée Lauder, First Response, Fisher Price, Foot Locker, GE, GTE, Holiday Inn, Hyundai, Interland, Lancaster (see also Joop!) (Box PB93)
    - 1993
      - Burroughs-Wellcome, Carter-Wallace (Box PB94)
      - TWA (Box PB95-96)
    - 1993-1994
      - Miller Brewing Company (Box PB97)
    - 1993-1995
      - British Airways (Box PB98)
    - 1994
      - Carter-Wallace, Falcon Jet, GECC (General Electric Capital Corporation), T. Rowe Price,Warner-Wellcome, Wendy's, Westvaco (Box PB99)
      - Cunard (Box PB100)
      - General Felt, Kal Kan, M & M/Mars (Box PB101)
      - Lancaster (see also Joop!), Mustang (Joop! jeans) (Box PB102)
      - New York Racing Association (Box PB103)
      - TWA (Box PB104-105)
    - 1994-1995
      - Caribbean Tourism, Chemical Geoserve, Foot Locker (Box PB106)
    - 1995
      - Carter-Wallace, Foot Locker, Warner-Wellcome (Box PB107)
      - Champs, Cunard, Texaco (Box PB108)
    - 1995-1996
      - Alcon, Davis and Geck, CBS, Heublein (Box PB109)
      - Army, Howard Johnson (HoJo), GECC (General Electric Capital Corporation), Origins, Perrier (Box PB110)
      - Aruba Tourism, Caribbean Tourism, Condado Plaza, General Felt, Israel Ministry of Tourism (Box PB111)
      - Campbell's, Miller Brewing Company (Box PB112)
      - Estée Lauder (Box PB113)
      - Kal Kan, M & M/Mars, Maxell (Box PB114)
      - Lancaster (see also Joop!), Mustang (Joop! Jeans) (Box PB115)
    - 1995-1997
      - Chase Chemical, Westvaco (Box PB116)
      - Clinique, ProPlayer, Prescriptives (Box PB117)
    - 1995-2003
      - Brown & Williamson (Kool, Lucky Strike), Carter-Wallace (Nair, Trojan), CDW, Estée Lauder, Help USA, Internet Security Systems, JRAP (Joint Recruiting Advertising Program), Murata, Sauza (Allied Domecq), T. Rowe Price, TAP Pharmaceuticals (Prevacid), Texaco, UUNet (see also MCI), Warner-Lambert (Benadryl, Desitin), Wendy's, Westvaco, Whitney Museum, Women's Fund of Central Indiana (Box PB118)
    - 1996-1997
      - Alcon, Davis and Geck, Carter-Wallace, Kinney (Box PB119)
      - Avis, Heublein, T. Rowe Price (Box PB120)
      - Best Foods, Foot Locker, Warner-Lambert (Box PB121)
      - Champs, Cunard, Texaco (Box PB122)
      - Chase Manhattan, DRM, EDS, Maxell (Box PB123)
    - 1996-2002
      - CDW, Estée Lauder, ISS (Internet Security Systems), Murata, UUNet (see also MCI), Wendy's (Box PB124)
    - 1996-2003
      - Benadryl (Warner-Lambert), Dentyne Ice, Hyundai, Lucky Strike (Brown & Williamson), T. Rowe Price, Verizon, Whitney Museum (Box PB125)
    - 1997-1999
      - Origins, Perrier, Ted Bates, Westvaco (Box PB126)
    - 1998
      - CBS (Box PB127)
      - Clinique, Cunard, CVS, Warner-Lambert (Box PB128)
    - 1998-1999
      - Allied Domecq (see also Sauza), Carter-Wallace, EDS, Partnership for a Drug Free America (Box PB129)
      - Avis, General Electric (GE), Heublein, MapQuest (Box PB130)
    - 1999
      - Cable and Wireless, Jose Cuervo, T. Rowe Price (Box PB131)
      - Clinique, Prevacid, Warner-Lambert, Wendy's (Box PB132)
  - Alphabetical List, 1957-2003
    Arranged by client, then by year
    - Ad Council (Backer Spielvogel Bates) 1993-1995, Box PB98 (Box PB132)
    - AIDS Foundation 1992-2001, Box PB93 (Box PB132)
    - Alcon
      - 1995-1996, Box PB109 (Box PB132)
      - 1996-1997, Box PB119 (Box PB132)
    - Allied Domecq 1998-1999, Box PB129 (Box PB132)
    - American Chicle
      - 1978-1979, Box PB7 (Box PB132)
      - 1980-1981, Box PB19 (Box PB132)
      - 1982-1983, Box PB33 (Box PB132)
    - American Cyanamid
      - 1982-1983, Box PB34 (Box PB132)
      - 1984-1986, Box PB46 (Box PB132)
      - 1987-1987, Box PB58 (Box PB132)
    - Arrid 1992-2001, Box PB93 (Box PB132)
    - Aruba Tourism 1995-1996, Box PB111 (Box PB132)
    - Avis
      - 1984-1986, Box PB44 (Box PB132)
      - 1987-1989, Box PB64 (Box PB132)
      - 1990-1990, Box PB77 (Box PB132)
      - 1992-1992, Box PB88 (Box PB132)
      - 1992-2001, Box PB93 (Box PB132)
      - 1996-1997, Box PB120 (Box PB132)
      - 1998-1999, Box PB130 (Box PB132)
    - Backer Spielvogel Bates
      - 1980-1982, Box PB28 (Box PB132)
      - 1989-1991, Box PB75 (Box PB132)
    - Benadryl (see also Warner-Lambert)
      - 1992-2001, Box PB93 (Box PB132)
      - 1996-2003, Boxes PB118, PB125 (Box PB132)
    - Best Foods
      - 1991-1993, Box PB86 (Box PB132)
      - 1992-1992, Box PB89 (Box PB132)
      - 1996-1997, Box PB121 (Box PB132)
    - Bonjour 1981-1983, Box PB30 (Box PB132)
    - Borden's
      - 1978-1979, Box PB8 (Box PB132)
      - 1980-1981, Box PB20 (Box PB132)
    - Breck
      - 1978-1979, Box PB8 (Box PB132)
      - 1980-1981, Box PB20 (Box PB132)
    - Brightlane.com 1992-2001, Box PB93 (Box PB132)
    - Bristol Myers 1978-1979, Box PB9 (Box PB132)
    - British Airways
      - 1989-1989, Box PB71 (Box PB132)
      - 1990-1990, Box PB78 (Box PB132)
      - 1991-1993, Box PB86 (Box PB132)
    - Burroughs Wellcome (see also Warner-Wellcome)
      - 1989-1992, Box PB76 (Box PB132)
      - 1992-1992, Box PB89 (Box PB132)
      - 1993-1993, Box PB94 (Box PB132)
    - Cable and Wireless 1999-1999, Box PB131 (Box PB132)
    - Cabletrom 1992-2001, Box PB93 (Box PB132)
    - Calgary (see also Miller Brewing Company) 1982-1983, Box PB40 (Box PB132)
    - Campbell's
      - 1980-1982, Box PB28 (Box PB132)
      - 1983-1988, Box PB43 (Box PB132)
      - 1989-1992, Box PB76 (Box PB132)
      - 1992-1994, Box PB92 (Box PB132)
      - 1992-2001, Box PB93 (Box PB132)
      - 1995-1996, Box PB112 (Box PB132)
    - Caribbean Tourism
      - 1992-2001, Box PB93 (Box PB132)
      - 1994-1995, Box PB106 (Box PB132)
      - 1995-1996, Box PB111 (Box PB132)
    - Carter-Wallace (see also Nair, Trojan)
      - 1978-1979, Box PB10 (Box PB132)
      - 1980-1981, Box PB21 (Box PB132)
      - 1982-1983, Box PB34 (Box PB132)
      - 1984-1986, Box PB46 (Box PB132)
      - 1987-1987, Box PB58 (Box PB132)
      - 1988-1988, Box PB66 (Box PB132)
      - 1992-1992, Box PB89 (Box PB132)
      - 1993-1993, Box PB94 (Box PB132)
      - 1994-1994, Box PB99 (Box PB132)
      - 1995-1995, Box PB107 (Box PB132)
      - 1996-1997, Box PB119 (Box PB132)
      - 1998-1999, Box PB129 (Box PB132)
    - CBS
      - 1987-1989, Box PB65 (Box PB132)
      - 1990-1992, Box PB82 (Box PB132)
      - 1995-1996, Box PB109 (Box PB132)
      - 1998-1998, Box PB127 (Box PB132)
    - CDW
      - 1992-2001, Box PB93 (Box PB132)
      - 1995-2003, Box PB118 (Box PB132)
      - 1996-2002, Box PB124 (Box PB132)
    - Champs
      - 1992-2001, Box PB93 (Box PB132)
      - 1995-1995, Box PB108 (Box PB132)
      - 1996-1997, Box PB122 (Box PB132)
    - Chase 1996-1997, Box PB123 (Box PB132)
    - Chase Chemical 1995-1997, Box PB116 (Box PB132)
    - Chase Manhatten 1978-1979, Box PB10 (Box PB132)
    - Chemical Geoserve 1994-1995, Box PB106 (Box PB132)
    - Cinemax
      - 1984-1986, Boxes PB46 (Box PB132)
      - 1987, Box PB58A (Box PB132)
      - 1988-1988, Box PB67 (Box PB132)
    - Cinnaburst (see also Warner-Lambert) 1992-2001, Box PB93 (Box PB132)
    - Clairol 1980-1981, Box PB21 (Box PB132)
    - Clinique